icmrindia.org 2016-03-10

# Privacy Policy | Case Studies | Case Study in Business, Management| Case Volumes | Case Pack

  | 

IBS Center For Management Research (ICMR) is committed to respecting your privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of personal information you share with us (such as name, email Id, address, phone no., etc). We believe it is important for you to know, how we treat the information about you, which we receive on the Internet.

In general, you can visit www.icmrindia.org on the World Wide Web without informing us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. However, our Web Servers track the domain names from which people visit us and analyze this data for trends and statistics, but the individual user remains anonymous. We use this information to measure the use of our site and to improve the content of our site. There are at times, when we may collect personal information such as your name, address, email id etc., from you. It is our intent to inform you before we do that and tell you what we intend to do with the information. Usually, the personal information we collect is used only by us to respond to your inquiry, process an order or allow you to access specific sections. If you choose not to provide the details we request, you can still visit most of the sections of the ICMR Website, but you may not be able to access certain features, sections and services like Online Shopping.

ICMR does not engage in or support spamming or misuse of email addresses.

We do our best to maintain the accuracy of personal information you supply to us; we are working on tools that will allow you to review and update your information in the future. We will take appropriate steps to protect the information you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. 

We are committed to privacy. Personal data privacy is a new and evolving area, and ICMR is evolving to meet these demands. Mistakes are possible; miscommunication is possible. If you have any comments, suggestions or questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at [info@icmrindia.org](mailto:info@icmrindia.org). We will address any issue to the best of our abilities. 

[www.icmrindia.org](http://www.icmrindia.org/ "Case Studies | Case Study in Business, Management, Operations, Strategy") may contain links to other sites. While we try to link to only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by other sites. 

By using this site, you signify your acceptance to the ICMR Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of the ICMR Website following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. 

We thank you for your support of these policies.

|     
---|---|---
